Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-the-thanh-pmp®-47526a76 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Structural Engineering
Steel Design
Concrete

Certifications

Project Management Professional (PMP)

Nguyen The Thanh, PMP®

Project Manager

Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Project Coordinator and Civil & Structural Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the residential/commercial real estate industry. Skilled in both Design Construction. Strong in project management with Project Management Professional (PMP) Certificate from Project Management Institute - USA

Experience

Mapletree Project Manager September 2023 - Present (1 year 7 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Keppel Land Vietnam
Lead Coordinator and C&S Manager
December 2016 - August 2022 (5 years 9 months)

P&T Architects and Engineers Ltd Senior Structural Engineer September 2010 - November 2016 (6 years 3 months)

ICP (QACC) Consultant Structural Design Engineer October 2009 - July 2010 (10 months)

Education

HCM University of Architecture

Bachelor's degree, Structural Engineering (2005 - 2010)